Guide to the Edward H. Boos Photographs 1897-1907
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- A Hunting Party, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-475)
  Duplicate of 78-435
- By the Lonesome Brook, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-476)
  Duplicate of 78-395
- Harvesting in the Flathead Valley, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-477)
  Duplicate of 78-430
- Harvesting in the Flathead Valley, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-478)
- Mission Creek, undated (Box-folder 6/3, Photo number 672-479)
  Duplicate of 78-397
- Funeral for unidentified person, etched printing plate, undated (Box-folder 6/4, Photo number 672-480)
- Unidentified lake, undated (Box-folder 6/5)
- Order booklets for "Flathead Indian Pictures", undated (Box-folder 6/6)